{
    "id": "71e9fd6c046b4b2aa7cf7be0b0af3633",
    "title": "Sentence correction: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "39d020a40d7d4fb69bd8df4f7afe2114",
            "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Sid can play tennis as ................................ as his brother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The match had hardly begun .................................. it started raining.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "when",
                        "than"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That was ...................................... a mistake.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sure",
                        "surely"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He talks more .......................................... than his brother. Needless to say, he is the more popular of the two.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "pleasant",
                        "pleasantly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When you become a parent, you will think .................................... about children.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "different",
                        "differently"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I felt ...................................... about not having won the championship.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bad",
                        "badly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Winning is not ...................................... as important as playing well.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "near",
                        "nearly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His behavior seemed a little ............................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "oddly",
                        "odd"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He didnâ€™t run ....................................... enough to qualify for the race.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We could ............................................ see the snow-capped mountains at a distance.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "clear",
                        "clearly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}